Lu Xing!
لو شينغ!
Xing!
Xing!
Call an ambulance!
اتصل بالإسعاف!
Move!
تحرك!
Wait here.
انتظر هنا.
My parents divorced when I was a child.
انفصل والداي عندما كنت طفلاً.
I grew up with my grandfather
نشأت مع جدي
until he died.
حتى مات.
I lost my family
لقد فقدت عائلتي
was gone too.
لقد رحل أيضاً.
Later,
لاحقاً،
I was hunted by Lin Mojiao
لقد طاردني لين موجياو
for investigating Vivi's family.
للتحقيق في عائلة فيفي.
You took me home and helped me
أخذتني إلى المنزل وساعدتني
avoid Lin Mojiao's
تجنب مطعم لين موجياو
investigation.
تحقيق.
I'm warning you,
أحذرك،
don't die in my house.
لا تموت في بيتي.
Or I'll make sure you won't rest in peace.
وإلا سأضمن ألا تنعم بالراحة الأبدية.
Get up.
استيقظ.
Why isn't your wound healing?
لماذا لا يلتئم جرحك؟
Are you taking your medicine?
هل تتناول دوائك؟
Yes.
نعم.
Then drink it.
ثم اشربه.
Do I need to feed you?
هل عليّ أن أطعمك؟
No.
لا.
I'm really picking up a trouble.
أشعر حقاً أنني أواجه مشكلة.
If Lin Mojiao wasn't looking for you,
إذا لم تكن لين موجياو تبحث عنك،
I wouldn't have to take care of you.
لن أكون مضطراً لرعايتك.
I would just throw you in the hospital.
سأقوم بإيداعك في المستشفى.
Although
بالرغم من
you always say harsh words,
أنت دائماً تقول كلمات قاسية،
you are actually
أنت في الواقع
you are a very gentle person.
أنت شخص لطيف للغاية.
Miss Zhu.
الآنسة تشو.
You...
أنت...
Lin Moqing.
لين موكينج.
You jerk.
يا لك من أحمق.
Why don't you like me?
لماذا لا تحبني؟
What's wrong with me?
ما الذي يحدث لي؟
You are good.
أنت جيد.
Liar.
كذاب.
Big liar.
كاذب كبير.
I...
أنا...
I didn't.
لم أكن.
I'm glad
أنا سعيد
I stayed.
مكثت.
I'm glad I stayed by your side.
أنا سعيد لأنني بقيت بجانبك.
You never abandoned me.
لم تتخل عني أبداً.
Why do you always listen to me?
لماذا تستمع إليّ دائماً؟
You do whatever I say.
ستفعل كل ما أقوله.
Are you willing to be someone's dog?
هل أنت مستعد لأن تكون كلباً لأحدهم؟
You said
أنت قلت
as long as I live here,
طالما أنني أعيش هنا،
I have to listen to you.
يجب أن أستمع إليك.
Besides,
بجانب،
you really helped me a lot.
لقد ساعدتني كثيراً.
Do you think
هل تعتقد
this child is yours?
هل هذا الطفل ابنك؟
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
Lu Xing,
لو شينغ,
I'm tired of this.
لقد سئمت من هذا.
Let's break up.
فلننفصل.
No matter who the father is,
بغض النظر عن هوية الأب،
as long as Wenjie wants the baby,
طالما أن وينجي تريد الطفل،
I'll take care of them for the rest of my life.
سأعتني بهم طوال حياتي.
How is he now?
كيف حاله الآن؟
The patient's condition is extremely unstable.
حالة المريض غير مستقرة للغاية.
He has dissociative identity disorder and intermittent attacks.
يعاني من اضطراب الهوية الانفصامية ونوبات متقطعة.
He is now in the compulsory treatment stage,
هو الآن في مرحلة العلاج الإلزامي،
and cannot cooperate with the police for the time being.
ولا يمكنه التعاون مع الشرطة في الوقت الحالي.
We need to wait for the judicial expertise results.
علينا انتظار نتائج الخبرة القضائية.
Doctor,
طبيب،
can I talk to him alone?
هل يمكنني التحدث معه على انفراد؟
I'll go with you.
سأذهب معك.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
I can.
أنا استطيع.
I'll wait for you at the door.
سأنتظرك عند الباب.
When Vivi first
عندما كانت فيفي لأول مرة
mentioned you to me,
ذكرك لي،
I had never seen her so happy.
لم أرها قط بهذه السعادة.
She has a whole box of diaries,
لديها صندوق كامل من المذكرات،
all about you.
كل شيء يدور حولك.
She never lied from childhood to adulthood,
لم تكذب قط منذ طفولتها وحتى بلوغها سن الرشد.
but for you,
أما بالنسبة لك،
she deceived all of us.
لقد خدعتنا جميعاً.
But you lied to her,
لكنك كذبت عليها،
used her,
استغلها،
and killed her.
وقتلها.
Why?
لماذا؟
Why are you still
لماذا ما زلتَ كذلك؟
alive here now?
هل أنت على قيد الحياة هنا الآن؟
You'd better
من الأفضل لك
[rot here for the rest of your life.]
[ستتعفن هنا لبقية حياتك.]
[Don't ever leave.]
[لا تغادر أبداً.]
[The number you've dialed is not available.]
[الرقم الذي طلبته غير متاح.]
Hello, Dad.
مرحباً يا أبي.
Mom is sick.
أمي مريضة.
When are you coming back?
متى ستعود؟
I can't cut it.
لا أستطيع فعل ذلك.
Don't cut the bomb.
لا تقطع القنبلة.
Dad.
أب.
[Who are you talking to?]
[مع من تتحدث؟]
[I'm busy.] I won't come back yet.
أنا مشغول. لن أعود الآن.
Just pour some hot water for your mom.
صبّي بعض الماء الساخن لأمك.
Dad,
أب،
I'm hungry.
أنا جائع.
Go to your mom.
اذهب إلى والدتك.
That's it for now.
هذا كل شيء في الوقت الحالي.
I'll come back when I'm free.
سأعود عندما أكون متفرغاً.
Happy birthday to you.
عيد ميلاد سعيد.
Come on.
تعال.
Let's blow out the candles together.
هيا نطفئ الشموع معاً.
Baby, you're a year older.
يا صغيري، لقد كبرت عاماً.
Are you happy?
هل أنت سعيد؟
Yes.
نعم.
Daddy has prepared a gift for you.
لقد أعدّ أبي هدية لك.
Come on.
تعال.
Let's take a look.
دعونا نلقي نظرة.
Here it is.
ها هو.
What could be in such a big box?
ما الذي يمكن أن يكون موجوداً في مثل هذا الصندوق الكبير؟
Look.
ينظر.
That's amazing. Do you like it?
هذا رائع. هل أعجبك؟
It's all your fault.
كل هذا خطأك.
It's not my fault.
ليس هذا خطأي.
You all deserve to die.
جميعكم تستحقون الموت.